# 雷神之锤斜挎包
Mjölnir bag
# 做了一个雷神锤的斜挎包
I made a Mjölnir bag
# 看一下
take a look
# 它这里可以打开
you can open it here
# 里面有个盒子，可以装一些
there's a box that can hold
# 打火机
lighter
# 手机啊
phone
# 卫生纸
tissue
# 钱包之类的
wallet, and other stuff
# 旋转雨伞
swiveling umbrella
# 雨季马上就要到了，平时我们下雨打伞
the wet season is coming
# 尤其是2个人打一把伞的时候，由于雨伞面积的原因
especially when there're two people under the same umbrella
# 经常会打湿自己的肩膀
we may have a wet shoulder due to the size of the umbrella
# 现在不会了
you won't experience this anymore
# 我发明的这种可以旋转的雨伞
because I have invented a swiveling umbrella
# 看到没，这里有个小按钮，只要你轻轻地一按
look, there's a small button here, and if you press it
# 它就会快速地转动，通过强大的离心力，把雨水甩出去
it will start swiveling swiftly. With the help of a strong centrifugal force, it can throw the waterdrops away
# 这样就不会打湿自己的肩膀
so that you won't get wet in your shoulder
# 希望红心点点，关注一下
if you like it, please hit the like and subscribe buttons.
# 下雨的时候给大家演示
I'll show you when it's rainy
# 给大家看看这个雨伞在下雨天的时候是什么样的
let me show you how it functions on a rainy day
# 看到没有
see?
# 也没有说，特别，转得特别干嘛
It's not like... very... you know
# 也打湿不了肩膀
And you shoulders won't be wet
# 便携板凳
portable stool
# 平时我们在等公交
when we're waiting for the bus
# 或地铁的时候
or subways
# 经常为找不到
we often worry about
# 一个座位而发愁犯难
not being able to find a seat.
# 所以说这几天我一直在研究一个小板凳
These days, I've been researching on a new stool
# 它的外表很难看出是一个小板凳来
it doesn't look like a stool in appearance
# 下面我给大家演示一下怎么用
let me show you how it works
# 首先把松紧带放进去
insert the elastic bands
# 然后再穿进去就可以了
then put in your feet
# 这就是穿好的样子
this is how it looks on your feet
# 也不会影响我们走路，当你累的时候
doesn't affect walking, and when you feel tired
# 直接蹲下就可以
just sit on it
# 它会卸掉人体大部分的力量
it will take off most of your weight and
# 而且坐多久都不会觉得累
you won't feel tired no matter how long you sit
# 这样你就可以走在哪里坐在哪里
you can sit wherever you go
# 当你想找个地方坐的时候甚至都不用起身
when you want to sit you won't even need to get up
# 看到没有
see?
# 就想这样非常方便
like this, super convenient
# 如果喜欢的话点个红心
if you like it, press the like button! thanks
# 改装摩托
modified motorbike
# 给大家看一下我刚改好的摩托车
take a look at my modified motorbike
# 外表跟普通的摩托车差不多
looks like an ordinary motorbike
# 但是说你打开它的坐垫
but if you open its seat
# 你就发现
you will find that
# 它是一个马桶
it's a toilet seat!
# 还可以冲水
you can even flush it
# 我给大家
let me
# 试一下
show you guys
# 吃蚂蚱
eating a locust